export const questions = [
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951ae6",
        "correctAnswer": "1997",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1982",
            "1967",
            "1952"
        ],
        "question": "In which year did the UK return Hong Kong sovereignty to China?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "628d54b2a5a57ff6c2ad2bf3",
        "correctAnswer": "Romanov",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nikolevsky",
            "Napoleon",
            "Lenin"
        ],
        "question": "What was the name of the reigning imperial house of Russia from the 17th century until the 1917 revolution?",
        "tags": [
            "russia",
            "leaders",
            "revolutions",
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "62611f7e4b176d54800e3d5d",
        "correctAnswer": "1961",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1947",
            "1954",
            "1968"
        ],
        "question": "In which year was the first human sent into space?",
        "tags": [
            "events",
            "firsts",
            "space_exploration",
            "exploration",
            "cold_war",
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a4e",
        "correctAnswer": "France",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Italy",
            "England",
            "China"
        ],
        "question": "The Eldest Sons Of The Kings Of Which Country Had The Title 'Dauphin'?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "62611fc74b176d54800e3d70",
        "correctAnswer": "1989",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1984",
            "1994",
            "1999"
        ],
        "question": "When did the scientist Tim Berners-Lee invent the World Wide Web?",
        "tags": [
            "events",
            "the_internet",
            "technology",
            "inventions",
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503d9",
        "correctAnswer": "Pacific",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Atlantic",
            "Indian",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "question": "What ocean was amelia earhart flying over when she disappeared",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f9503b5",
        "correctAnswer": "Paris",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "London",
            "Nanjing",
            "Amsterdam"
        ],
        "question": "Which City Did The Allies Liberate On August 25th 1944?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950405",
        "correctAnswer": "Jackie kennedy",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Michelle Obama",
            "Mary Todd Lincoln",
            "Barbara Bush"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the first First Lady to be received privately by the Pope? ",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951a3e",
        "correctAnswer": "Thermopylae",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Marathon",
            "Corinth",
            "Troy"
        ],
        "question": "Where was the Greek army of Leonides annihilated by Persians in 480BC?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "id": "622a1c3c7cc59eab6f951ae0",
        "correctAnswer": "1961",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "1938",
            "1945",
            "1953"
        ],
        "question": "In which year was the Berlin Wall constructed?",
        "tags": [
            "history"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "regions": []
    }
]